http://zipdebt.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
HomePrivacy Policy
ZipDebt Privacy Policy
Important information about your privacy and our service.
This privacy notice discloses the private practices, for www.zipdebt.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:
1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to or collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time.
You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given below:
• See what data we have about you, if any.
• Change/correct any data we have about you.
• Have us delete any data we have about you.
• Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page where you enter such information. While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 1-866-515-2360 or via email at info@zipdebt.com.
Effective Date: August 1, 2015
Search ZipDebt
ZipDebt Resources
Free Consumer Debt Relief eBook
Latest Blog Posts
ZipDebt Debt Relief — MAJOR ANNOUNCEMENT FOR 2020 and COVID-19: Full Service TAILORED DEBT SETTLEMENT Available for Select Clients, Do-It-Yourself Coaching & Services No Longer Offered
Making the Tough Financial Decision, Part 3 — Paying Off $63,000 Credit Card Debt & Lessons Learned
Making the Tough Financial Decision, Part 2 — Our Dream Home Goes on the Market
